Guide to Peter P. Carr Papers RG.055
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series XXVIII: Fixed Barrier Forward Valuations, 1998-2005
  - Put Call Ratio when Arrival Rates Depend on Spot, 2002-04-25-2005-02-01 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Reference Reports, 2002-05-01-2002-09-12 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Adjoint Interpretations of Put Call Reversal, 2005-02-20-2005-02-21 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Forward Barrier Write-up, 2005-09-17 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Double Knockout Call Forward P(I)DE, 2003-03-23-2005-09-20 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Penaud, Antony; Fast Valuation of a Portfolio of Barrier Options under Merton's Jump Diffusion Hypothesis, Wilmott 2004, Undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - American Digital Puts & DCBC's, 2003-03-27-2003-10-13 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - American Digital Put Call Ratio, 2002-12-07 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Robert V. Kohn's Notes on FPIDE with Jumps, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Wystup, Uwe; The Market Price of Foreign Exchange One-Touch Options, Derivatives Week 2003, Undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - (Applications to Valuing) Barrier Options, 2000-11-02-2001-07-21 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - American Digital Puts & ADC's, 2003-06-19 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - FBCPIDE, 2002-06-19 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Binary (European) Put Call Reversal, 2002-05-11-2002-05-17 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Contingent Notional, 2002-10-14 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Contingent Notional Put Call Ratio, 2002-03-18 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - FPDE for Down-and-In Binary Call/American Binary Put with Deferred Rebate, 2002-10-01-2002-10-18 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - American Binary Call/Put, 2002-01-24-2003-10-12 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Down and Out Call, FP(I)DE, k > H, 2001-05-06-2003-10-12 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - DCC FPIDE, k < L, 2003-01-20-2003-10-12 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - DOP/C Reversal, 2002-03-20-2003-03-29 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - UoC Put Call Ratio, 2002-03-18 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Up & Out Call Forward PIDE, 2005-02-20-2005-02-21 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Extracting First Passage Time Probability Density Function from Out Barrier Options, 2003-10-13 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - PDE's for First Passage Time Probability Density Functions, 2001-07-14-2003-03-01 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Forward Equation for First Passage Time Payer, 2002-04-30-2002-06-23 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Moustakides, George V.; Extension of Wald's First Lemma to Markov Processes, 2001-11-13 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Borovkov, K. & Burq, Z.; Kendall's Identity for the First Crossing Time Revisited, Electronic Communications in Probability 2001, 2002-06-19 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Integrating Out First Passage Time Probability Density Function, 1998-04-04 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Last Exit Time & First Passage Time, 2001-07-25-2002-03-24 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Model - Free Results, 2003-10-12 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Partial Barrier Options, 2000-07-25 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - (Barrier Options from) Stop Options, 2003-02-16-2003-03-03 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Series XXIX: Forward P(I)DE, 1986-2005
  - Panayotov, G. & Madan, D.; The COGARCH Model and Option Pricing, 2005-10-31 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Time Reversal Literature for Processes with Jumps, 1999-11-08-2000-11-24 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Literature on Duality, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Relevant Reviews, 2001-06-26 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Andersen, L. & Andreasen, J.; Jump-Diffusion Processes: Volatility Smile Fitting and Numerical Methods for Option Pricing, 2000-05-06 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Dellacherie, C.; Theorie Generale du Potentiel I, Undated (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Dynkin, E. B.; An Application of Flows to Time Shift and Time Reversal in Stochastic Processes 1985, Undated (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Errami, Russo & Vallois; Ito's Formula for C^1 lambda-Functions of a Cadlag Process and Related Calculus, 2001-02 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Jacod, J. & Protter, P.; Time Reversal on Lévy Processes, Annals of Probability 1988, Undated (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Madon, Dilip B.; The Instantaneous Profit and Loss Account, 2000-10-19-2002-03-13 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Nagasawa, Masao; Time Reversion of Markov Processes, Nagoya Mathematical Journal 1964, Undated (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Picard, J. & Savona, C.; Smoothness of Harmonic Functions and Time Reversal of Markov Processes, Undated (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Savine, A.; A Theory of Volatility, BNP-Paribas, Undated (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - BCPIDE, 2001-07-02-2002-02-24 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - BVPIDE, 2001-06-26-2002-04-12 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Call Consistency to Backward and Forward PIDE's, 2001-07-20-2002-03-07 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Derivation of Tanaka-Meyer from Taylor Series & Pure Jump Process, 2000-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Delta Measure vs. Share Measure, 2002-05-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Forward Call PIDE, 2000-2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Forward PIDE & Double Tail, 1999-2000; 60 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - FQ PIDE, 2001-2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - FV PIDE, 2001-2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Higher Order Term Representations in FCPIDE, 2002-02-2002-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Implications of PCR, 2002-05; 60 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Intrinsic Value Decomposition for Jump Processes, 1999-2000; 60 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Jumps, 2000-2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Jump Process Becomes Continuous?, 2002-05; 60 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Levy Process Results, 2001-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Local Double Tail & TR, 2001-07-28; 60 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Local Levy Density (& TR), 2001-2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - Local Variation, 2000-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - Maturity Restrictions in One Factor Markov World, 2000-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - Nature of Options, 2000-2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - SLSG, 2001; 60 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 69)
  - Stochastic Equivalences in Forward & Backward Economies, 2002-05; 60 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 70)
  - Stochastic Local Vol. & Levy Density, 2000-10-24; 60 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 71)
  - Stochastic Strike Process, 2001-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 72)
  - Time Reversability of Markov Semi-martingales, 2002-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 73)
  - Time Value Invariance, 2001-2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 74)
  - Why Only for Calls is FCPIDE Same Term as BCPIDE, 2001-06-2001-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 14, Folder 75)
- Series XXX: Forward P(I)DE for American Put, 1992-2003
  - A Forward PDE for American Puts in the Dupire Model, 2000-01-03-2003-03-12 (Box 14, Folder 76)
  - Schroder, M.; Changes of Numeraire for Pricing Futures, Forwards, and Options; Review of Financial Studies 1999, Undated (Box 14, Folder 77)
  - Arun's Put Call Relations, 2001-07-07-2001-07-18 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Chriss, Neil; Transatlantic Trees, Risk July 1996, 2001-05-07 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Detemple, J.; American Options: Symmetry Properties, 1999-03-02 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Wystup, U.; Aspects of Symmetry, Homogeneity and Duality of the Black-Scholes Pricing Formula for European Style Put and Call Options, 1999-01-20 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Peskir & Shiryaev, A Note on the Call-Put Parity and a Call-Put Duality, Undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Lewis, A.; Duality and Changes of Numeraire, Undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - FPDE for American Options in Heston Model, Undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - American Call on Stock Paying Known Dividend, 2002-10-16-2002-10-21 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Forward PDE for American Options via SLSG, 1992-02-2002-11-19 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - American FCPDE (True), 2001-06-08-2002-04-30 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - American Put Call Ratio, 2001-07-19-2003-03-04 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Envelope Theorem Approach, 2000-11-17-2003-03-02 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Forward PDE for American Options via Forward PDE for European Options, 2001-04-14 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Forward PDE for American Call with Continuous Ex Opp's, 2000-11-16 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - (Forward PDE for) American Calls in Terms of European Options, 2002-01-12-2002-01-19 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - (Using) Complex Variables, 2000-11-08-2001-03-28 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Schrodinger Equation, 2001-05-08 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Complex SBM via Time Reversal, 2001-03-21-2001-03-31 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Using Time Reversal to Create Adaptive Mesh or Tree, Undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Binomial Model, 2002-01-18-2002-01-19 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Binomial or Trinomial Illustration of Strike Maturity Arbitrage, 2001-07-25-2001-08-04 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Derman & Kani, Riding on a Smile, Risk February 1994, Undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Derman & Kani, The Volatility Smile and Its Implied Tree, 1993-12-29 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Derman, Kani & Zou; The Local Volatility Surface: Unlocking the Information in Index Option Prices, Financial Analysts Journal July/August 1996, Undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Kani, Derman & Kamal; Trading and Hedging Local Volatility, 1996-08 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Williams, Todd; Branching Process Stock Model, 2001 Dissertation, 2001-07-19 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Put Call Reversal Paper, 2002-02-22-2002-03-07 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Series XXXI: Frequently Asked Questions, 1993-2000
  - Arbitrage in BS Model with Unknown Vol., 2000-10-20 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - FAQ Revision for Journal of Derivatives, 2000-07-13-2000-12-12 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Journals, 2000-01-12-2000-01-26 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Mistake in BS Derivation, 1999-12-21 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Manuscript, 1999-12-21 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - MMI & RNV, 1999-06-13 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Eliminating Market Price of Risk, Undated (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - RNV as Quantoing, 1999-05-30-1999-06-01 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Law of the Unconscious Finance Professor (1), 1999-08-27 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - How Does Quantoing Work?, Undated (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Why Does RNV Work?, Undated (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Continuing Ed Credit, 1999-04-15 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Law of the Unconscious Finance Professor (2), 1999-06-09 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Irrelevance of Expected Return, 1999-03-29-1999-06-10 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Bergman, Yaacov; A Characterization of Self-Financing Portfolio Strategies, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Andreasen, Jensen & Poulsen; New Skin for the Old Ceremony: Eight Different Derivations of the Black-Scholes Formula, 1996-11-20; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Beck, Thomas; Black-Scholes Revisited: Some Important Details, 1993-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - RNV as Change of Numerative, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Hedging Trinomial Process in a Feasible Market, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - FAQ's at NMS, 1999; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - FAQ's in Option Pricing Theory, 1997-03-27; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - GT & Time Dependent Drifts, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Girsanov's Time & Quantity Randomization, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - FAQ's, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Girsanov's Theorem & Exchange Rates, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Siegel's Paradox for Stocks, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Girsanov's Theorem, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Ajay's Question, 1998-11-21; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 55)
- Series XXXII: Futures Exotic, 1993-1994
  - Galeeva, Roza; Evaluation of Forward Start Options in the Mean Reverting Environment, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Part I: Overview of Valuation Techniques and Exotic Structures (1), Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Carr, Peter; Asian Options; Overheads for Mobil Course, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Carr, Peter; Rainbow Options; Overheads for Mobil Course, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Part I: Overview of Valuation Techniques and Exotic Structures (2), Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Carr, Peter; American Futures Options; Overheads for Mobil Course, Undated; `; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Carr, Peter; Static Hedges for Barrier Options; Overheads for Mobil Course, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Appendix: Valuation of European Call on the Maximum of Two Futures Prices, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Mobil Seminar Receipts & Notes, 1994-09; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Mobil Seminar Overview, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Barrier Options, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Asian Spread Option Valuation, 1993; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Rainbow Options, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 68)
- Series XXXIII: Going with the Flow, 1957-2000
  - Contingent Accrual Notes, 1998-1999; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Cont. Cash Flow Rewrite, 2000-07-14; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Alternative Approach Rewrite, 2000-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Rollercoaster Puts, 1993-1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Pay as You Go on Futures, 1997-2000; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Journal of Finance Submission, 1999-11-1999-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - Pant, V.; PriceWaterhouseCoopers Risk Converence, A PDE Method for Computing Moments, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 75)
  - Fitzsimmons, P. & Pitman, J.; Kac's Moment Formula and the Feynman-Kac Formula for Additive Functionals of a Markov Process, 1998-05-29; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 76)
  - Representing an Option as a Time Strip of Options, 1999-09; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 77)
  - Miller, J.C.P.; Note on the General Solution of the Confluent Hypergeometric Equation, 1957; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 78)
  - CEV Special Case, 1999-04; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 79)
  - Linetsky & Davydov; Pricing Options on One-Dimensional Diffusions Unified Approach, 1999-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 15, Folder 80)
  - SL Equations, 1999-04-04; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Pay as You Go on Spot, 1998-1999; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Second Order Linear CDE's with No Middle Term, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Pay as You Go Corridor, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Ju, Nengjiu; Pricing an American Option by Approximating Its Early Exercise Boundary As a Multi-Piece Exponential Function, 1997-08-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Expl's of Cont. Paid Cash Flow, 1998-04; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Time Dependent Cash Flow, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Lewis, A.L.; Applications of Eigenfunction Expansions in Continuous-Time Finance, 1998-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Swap Pay-offs Involving Exterior, 1999-03-13; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Deferred Payout on Futures, 1998-1999; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Nikkei Linked to Dollar/Yen, 1998-01-1998-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Links with Asians, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Static Hedging of TIBS, 1998-02-14; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Broadie, Glasserman & Kou; A Continuity Correction for Discrete Barrier Options, 1995-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Series XXXIV: Half Baked Ideas, 1970-1995; 60 Linear Feet
  - Upper Bd on American Options, 1995-04; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Two Valued Drift, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Lognormal Wealth-log Util., Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Poisson Branching Process, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Paper with Roni, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Paper with John Abowd, 1991-11-01-1991-11-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Paper with Bruce Tuckman, 1992-05-1992-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Paper with Francis, 1990-1991; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Paper with Rajna, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Paper with Ren-Row, 1993-10-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Paper with Dave Heath, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Paper with Dave Shimko, 1992; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Paper with Bill Ziemba, 1990-1991; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Spot Rate as Bessel, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Compound Options, 1990-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Am Bin (American Binomials), 1992-02-19; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Ideas for Papers, 1986-1993; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Assets Paying $1 at Random Times, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Understanding the CAPM, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Exog. Process for Defaultible Coporate Debt, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Liquidity, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Option Pricing with Discrete Rebalancing, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Serial Correlation & Options, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Compound Option Pricing under Interest Rate Uncertainty, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Call on Exchange Option, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Volatility Signalling, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Currency & Interest Rate Swaps, Undated (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - The Effect of Asset Substitution on the Liabilities of the Firm, Undated (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Brownian Bridge Where Instantaneous Variance is a Function of Time, Undated (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Generalized Asset Pricing, Undated (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Foreign Currency & International Rate Options, 1985-11-07-1986-01-06 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Generalized Options, Undated (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Bond Options, 1971-04-16-1972-05-15 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Long Rate as Single Factor, Undated (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Duration of Contingent Claims, Undated (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Imperfect Loan Guarantee, Undated (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Futures Prices with Stochastic International Rates, 1987-03-16-1987-04-17 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Convertible Bonds, 1970-04-20-1986-06-30 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Comments & Revisions on Convertible Bonds, 1986-07 (Box 16, Folder 53)
- Series: XXXV: Hedging Barrier Options, 1999-2007
  - Elliot, Wang & Chen; Alternative Characterizations of American Options with Fractional Brownian Motion, 2002-12 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Bjork, T. & Hult, H.; A Note on the Self-Financing Condition for the Fractional Black-Scholes Model, 2003-02-20 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Replicating Barrier Options Under Poisson Jumps, 2006-12-16-2007-01-04 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Borges, C.F. & Peters C.S.; Computing Approximate Stationary Distributions for Discrete Markov Processes with Banded Infinitesimal Generators, 2007-01-02 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Steutel, F.W.; Poisson Processes and A Bessel Function Integral, 1985 Society for Industrial and Applied Mathematics, 2006-12-06 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Bermin, H.P.; Comment on 'Valuation of Barrier Options in a Black-Scholes Setup with Jump Risk', 1999 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Skellam Distribution, 2007-01-01 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Karlis, D. & Ntzoufras, I.; Bayesian Analysis of the Differences of Count Data, Statistics in Medicine, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Semi-Static Hedging of Barrier Options Under Poisson Jumps, 2007-01-02 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Dengler, H. & Jarrow, R.A.; Option Pricing using a Binomial Model with Random Time Steps (A Formal Model of Gamma Hedging), 1997, Undated (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Difference of 2 Poissons, 2001-01-01-2001-01-11 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Sequential Barrier Options, 2006-04-13 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Static Hedging of Barrier Options, 2006-08-11 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Static Hedging of a One Touch with Payment at Expiry in the Black-Scholes Model with Jump to Default, 2005-10-05-2006-11-02 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Vanna-Volga Method, 2005-09-06-2005-09-21 (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Carr, P. & Verma, A.; Pricing Barrier Options using Vanna-Volga Method, October 2005, 2005-11-01 (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - Vanna-Volga Approach, 2006-10-11 (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - Castagna, A. & Mercurio, F.; The Vanna-Volga Method for Implied Volatilities: Tractability and Robustness, Undated (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - Castagna, A. & Mercurio, F.; Consistent Pricing of FX Options, Undated (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - Semi Static Super & Sub Replication with Signed Asymmetry, Undated (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - Boundary Barrier Option Values by Boundary Skew to First Passage Time to Barrier, 2005-02-28 (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - Hedging Barriers, 2006-03 (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - Regression to Determine Market Price and Risk, Undated (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - One Touch Hedge, 2005-10-05 (Box 16, Folder 77)
  - Carr, P. & Wu, L; Hedging Barriers, 2006-01-27-2006-04-20 (Box 16, Folder 78)
- Series XXXVI: HP12C Calculator, 1984-1998
  - Service Agreement, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Books - Coupon, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Programmable Calculators Article, 1993-09; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - HP17B Calculator, 1993-08-1995-09; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - HP19B II Calculator, 1993-11-29; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - List of Calculators, 1992; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Accessories for Calculators, 1990-1991; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - A Calculator Program for Option Values and Implied Standard Deviations, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Chapter 3 - Calculator Notes & Financial Functions, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Black Scholes Formula for FX Call, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - HP12C Software, 1984; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Basic Option Pricing Program 72 lines, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Basic Option Pricing Program 69 lines, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Basic Option Pricing Program 73 lines, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Black Formula for Call & All Derivatives, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Black Scholes Formula for Call and All Derivatives (No Dividends), Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Derivatives, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Duration Program, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - User Friendly Option Program, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Growing Annuities Trick, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - JFED Paper, 1988; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Copies of ISD Program, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Two Asset Portfolio Mean and Standard Deviation, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Series XXXVII: Ideas A-F, 1986-1999
  - Calculus of Variations Approximation of American Put, 1999-06-13; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - AMOL Results, 1996-03-28; 60 Linear Feet (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Appendix: Useful Facts About Normal Distributions, 1995-02-12 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Academic vs. Practitioner Perspectives, Undated (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Adding Dividends to a Model, 1997-06-19 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Analytic Valuation of Time Dependent Barrier Options, Undated (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Approximations, Undated (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Arbitrage Pricing vs. Liquidity Trader, Undated (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Valuing American Put in BS Model via T(S), Undated (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Myneni, Ravi; Notes on the American Equity Put Option, 1989-08-1997-07-29 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Little, Tom; Untitled - Free Boundary for American Put in BS Model, 1997-11-25 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Elliott, Geman & Madan; Beyond the American Put, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Linz, Peter; Numerical Methods for Volterra Integral Equations with Singular Kernels, September 1969, 1998-01-19 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Azema Martingales, Undated (Box 17, Folder 37)